[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_ChooseInstrument",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you have an instrument I could borrow?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Well now, that is a MOST curious request. Are you a lover of music? An artisan, perhaps? \\n\\nIt so happens that I carry a flute, should I be in a musical mood. As long as you solemnly swear to return it, you may borrow it.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_PlayForTown",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"A composer by the name of Marsyas.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I will remember that name. Do convey my appreciation for this work, should you meet again. \\n\\nYou simply must share this with Captain Dubois. You will find him near the Governor's hall. Oh, and keep the flute. My treat.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0403a_Huntsman_TaskTopic_DeliverPotions",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Better. A miracle elixir.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Let me guess, one of Anwir's? Don't look surprised, I've lived in Everfall at least as long as that old rascal. \\n\\nWell, nothing from Anwir's killed me yet. Bottoms up, and give him my regards, will you?",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_ChooseInstrument",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Actually, can I borrow that upright bass?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "It is quite heavy. I would hate for you to hurt yourself... But I suppose the moon and planets are aligned in a way that suggests better luck. \\n\\nYes. You may. Return it in a timely manner, please.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_PlayForTown",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Marsyas is the composer, not me.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ah! A bard, then! How kind of you to bring this melody to us! I shall ensure that Marsyas receives proper recognition. Do be sure to inform them of my generosity! \\n\\nNow, you must play for the masses! To the tavern with you!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0440a_00_AtticusDelphi_TaskTopic_DeliverPotions",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You're welcome to try it.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "The label says it cures all aches, ailments, and heartaches? How could a potion cure heartache? \\n\\nMmm, I do feel less tense after a few sips. That's a pleasant surprise in these trying times. Thank you.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0410_Barkeep_TaskTopic_PlayForTown",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll let composer Marsyas know.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Is that their name? I'll be sure to ask other bards if they know any of Marsyas's songs. \\n\\nI appreciate you breaking up the quiet with that bit of joy.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0410a_Barkeep_TaskTopic_SaveBar",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Jacob sent it.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Jacob? Jacob Evans? Good gracious, that poor kind man. \\n\\nHe's suffered so, yet he still thinks of me and my humble little establishment.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0441a_SairaYangandul_TaskTopic_EarnAudience",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Can you help me meet with your employer?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Lord Shen is particular about his company. You might be a bit too… dusty… to garner the right kind of attention. \\n\\nLuckily, Atticus is not. Don't act surprised, I know what you're after. I can help you both, for a price. In fact, I have a list.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0441a_SairaYangandul_TaskTopic_EarnAudience_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I've taken care of your errands.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "And I trust the parcel was delivered to the correct address. Good. \\n\\nA courier will seek out Atticus with an invitation. He is not to be late. He must be well-dressed and carry himself as a musician, not a butler. Understood?",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0442a_ConcettaSacco_TaskTopic_EarnPatron",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Lord Shen wishes to negotiate with you.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "He would. He knows what it would mean for him to woo my manservant. How it would stain the family name! \\n\\nHe does it for his own pride, not for Atticus' sake. No. I will accept no offer!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0442a_ConcettaSacco_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Lord Shen sent me with this.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Let me see it. Oh… oh, my. How grand. How generous. Perhaps he is not the fiend I thought. \\n\\nHe has such lovely taste in parchment. What a lovely texture. With great regret and sorrow, I do accept his offer.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0432a_OuShen_TaskTopic_EarnPatron",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"And what might that be?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I cannot employ one who is already sworn to another. I must come to an acceptable arrangement with Lady Sacco. \\n\\nIt would wound her pride to surrender him to me, but I suppose that is the point. Ask her to name her price.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0432a_OuShen_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She refused to part with him at all.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "How amusing. She thinks herself above temptation. Well, I can see that corrected. \\n\\nI prepared an initial offering. Deliver it to her, if you would. And do not open it, or I shall have your head.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_ReturnStaff",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I've come to fight back the Corruption.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Is THAT what all this hustle and bustle was about? My friend, we are perfectly capable of mounting a defense. Our guards are the finest in Aeternum. \\n\\nWhy not rest a while, perhaps leave some coin at our fine establishments?",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0403a_Huntsman_TaskTopic_AskAboutAdiana",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm looking for a huntress. Know of anyone?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "The women here are not exactly the rugged sort, if you take my meaning. \\n\\nThough the ever-so-charming Tekla-- er, Artificer Petrowski-- may know. She IS the sort to traipse around in the woods.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_ReturnStaff",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I came to help you fight the Corrupted.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "The Corrupted? You should know it is HORRIBLE bad luck to utter the name of the enemy aloud! \\n\\nNo, no, no, I'll not have you summon a dark cloud over this peaceful town! I must ask you to leave at once.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0405a_Artificer_TaskTopic_AskAboutAdiana",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"He said you could help me find a huntress.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "He did, did he? I've heard rumors about a strange woman who lives alone in the woods, but it smacks of gossip and folklore to me. \\n\\nMayhaps there's someone who deals in gossip that could tell you more.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0440a_Atticus_TaskTopic_RumorsMSQ",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm looking for an old fisherman named Yonas.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Can't say that name sparks any torches, perhaps he was just passing through? \\n\\nIf that's the case, I'd ask Guard Captain Dubois. He keeps his eye on who's coming and going.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0441a_Saira_TaskTopic_RumorsMSQ",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The guard said you could help find someone.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Did he? I'll have to give him a talking to. Gossip is more valuable than gold in this town. \\n\\nBut I'll give you this tip for free: if you're looking for someone recent, speak to the butler, Atticus. He knows everyone.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0450a_TownGuard_TaskTopic_RumorsMSQ",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Actually, I'm looking for someone.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Aren't we all? But information is power here. What you know, who you know… it could get you thrown down a hole somewhere. \\n\\nIf you're determined, look for Saira. She knows things, whether she admits it or not.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
